

Fuad Abdullah Front-End Developer

22880 Wedel
015788062638
Fuad-abdullah@outlook.com
www.linkedin.com/in/fuad-web
www.github.com/fuad221

Since the beginning of my career, I'm very self-driven and task orientated. I used to participate in workshops in developing work programs with programming specialists.

During my work for an international company in the human resources and education departments, I gained good experience about the needs of companies in digital systems, and the identification of new cultures increased the level of my understanding of the different needs of each society.

Educational Background

DCI - Digital Career Institute GmbH
Web Development
Intensive training on Web
Development topics from Front to
Backend with practical projects.

08/2020 - 09/2021

Hamburg, Germany

ZAL - Center for training and further education Analytical applications of spectroscopic methods such as (NMR, MS, UV / VIS, IR) spectroscopy

08/2019 - 09/2019

Luckenwalde, Berlin

Master's degree at Kazan Federal University Medical Physics

09/2013 - 06/2015

Kazan, Russia

Bachelor's degree at Taiz
University
Physics for a teaching position

09/2002 - 06/2005

Taiz, Yemen

Lecturer for physics target group profes-sionals - Part-time job Al-Saeed Academy

05/2009 - 09/2011

Taiz, Yemen

Work Experience

Stk softwire Technologie Kontor & Development Frontend web developer

12/2021 - 11/2022

Working with Javascript, Vue, Typescript and SQL

Hamburg, Germany

Freelancer

Web Marketing and Advertising

Wedel, Germany

Human Development Specialist Al-Saeed Academy

05/2009 - 09/2011

Training and evaluation of training programs and pre-paring training plans.

Taiz, Yemen

Lecturer for physics target group profes-sionals - Part-time job Al-Saeed Academy

05/2009 - 09/2011

Physics teacher for technical students

Taiz, Yemen

Head of HR department Hadramaut Industrial Complex, Hadramaut

03/2009 - 05/2009

HR Head: Workforce for 500 employees

Hadramaut, Yemen

Human resource development Hayel Saeed Anam Group of Companies

03/2007 - 03/2009

Planning and preparing training programs for HAS Group.

Taiz, Yemen

Work in data collection Al-Takamol for trading & marketing

03/2006 - 10/2006

Data collection and statistical analysis of human resources, insurance and movement departments and transportation

Taiz, Yemen

Education in the fire brigade

Dealing with hazards, extinguishing fires

09/2019 - 11/2020

Wedel, Germany

Skills & Proficiencies

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, material ui
- Ui / UX Design
- JavaScript, React, Redux, Vue, TypeScript
- Testing Framework Jest
- Python (basics)
- nodejs, MongoDb, SOL
- github, git
- Photoshop, XD, 3D blander

Language

Arabic Mother tongue

English Professional Working

Proficiency

German Limited Working

Proficiency

Russian Basic Working Proficiency

Lecturer in medical physics Taiz High Institute for Health and Applied Sciences

09/2005 - 02/2006

Taiz, Yemen

Volunteer Work & Certification

STK Consulting GmbH internship with Vue and Typescript

08.12 - 22.12/2021

Hamburg, Germany

Fire Department- Wedel Volunteer in the fire brigade

11/2020 - present

Wedel, Germany

Mindchase

Mindchase for Training and education company

08/2020

I had working on website on Front-end and Back-end by Material ui, javascript, React, Nodejs

Hamburg, Germany

HSA Group

Thanks certificates and appreciation from companies in the field of training and implementing programs to increase work speed and reduce errors during work.

2007 - 2010

Taiz, Yemen